1second.com 2008-12-17

# 1second.com Privacy Policy

When you provide your personal information (such as name, address, phone number, company name, email address, credit card or other financial information) ** we will never give or sell any of your individual information to anyone. **We will maintain the confidentiality of your personal information and **it will be used only to support your customer relationship with** **us**.

**All** of the sensitive financial information, (like credit card numbers), you transfer to us, using our order forms, is processed by **100% secure** servers (SSL), with the highest standards of encryption and security in the industry.

All exchanges between you and us will remain _confidential_ with no personally identifiable information being sold or provided to any third party. 

This includes: 

IP addresses and other information (browser, platform, referral URL etc.) contained in web server logs 

E-mail addresses contained in messages sent to us.

Credit card or other financial information.

Names, addresses, telephone numbers, etc.

Our pages with customers ads contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

You _will not receive any unsolicited e-mail_ from us unless you sign up for planned notification services, submitted an e-mail requiring a response and/or subscribed to a mailing list. 

.  
By using our Web sites and any or all of it's pages for your own advertising and/or promotional purposes and disclosing you name, phone number, email or any other contact information in your own ad(s), you are aware that this information is accessible to any visitor who may see your ad(s) online.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

So, please use our sites with confidence and the very best regards to you from everyone here at **1second.com**

If you have any questions, or to report any instances of abuse please contact [CUSTOMER SUPPORT](http://www.1second.com/ppc-customer.htm).
